start thanks for joining my session
开始感谢您参加我的会议
scope advanced leave or on setup
范围高级休假或设置
authoring and I want to tell you how to
创作，我想告诉你如何
write whom setup to to create your
写出要创建的人设置
workspace setups with this great tool
使用这个出色的工具进行工作区设置
called roof and I'm very happy to have
叫屋顶，我很高兴有
ad mercs are the offer of in fear and in
广告是恐惧中的提供
the audience it don't think that you can
观众认为您不能
learn anything but you can always
学到什么，但你可以永远
explain when I'm doing something wrong
解释我做错什么的时候
here so I'm yeah this is give me some
在这里，我是的，这是给我一些
pressure I am a user of film so that's
我是电影的使用者，所以
that's a good actually and I'm
其实很好，我是
responsible from to write the room setup
负责编写房间设置
for the X text project and I think this
X文字专案，我认为
is also one of the more advanced apps at
还是以下更高级的应用之一
Eclipse and I want to show you yeah what
Eclipse，我想告诉你是什么
you can learn from existing setups so
您可以从现有设置中学习
first let's have a look how a typical
首先让我们看一下
setup looks like maybe first the
设置看起来像首先
question who has ever wrote that we've
问题是谁曾经写过我们
set up okay that's well many of you okay
设置好，很多人都可以
cool so let's see what you can take off
很酷，让我们看看你可以起飞什么
that for the others um it's around 1/2
对于其他人来说，大约是1/2
that did not often we've set up let's
那不是我们经常设置的
have a look
看一看
Illume setup is basically a model
错觉设置基本上是一个模型
describing how to are to create and
描述如何创建和
provision and Eclipse IDE including
供应和Eclipse IDE，包括
features doing preferences import
进行首选项导入的功能
projects and so and this is the example
项目等等，这就是示例
from the JDT project at first we have
首先从JDT项目开始
the p2 director you know what the
P2主管，您知道
typically to director does that's on the
通常对导演来说
software which installs features for you
为您安装功能的软件
in your Clips so description that you
在剪辑中这样描述
want to install something in
想在里面安装东西
additionally to your Eclipse the here
除了您的Eclipse，这里
this case the EP de API tools then you
在这种情况下，使用EP de API工具
have some preferences that you set up in
有一些您在其中设置的偏好设置
your workspace you can influence the
您的工作空间可以影响
eclipse in a to set a heap size of your
蚀设置您的堆大小
Eclipse or whatever JVM parameters and
Eclipse或任何JVM参数以及
you can also create some resources or
您还可以创建一些资源或
files with a certain content which is
具有特定内容的文件是
placed at the certain position we go to
放在我们要去的某个位置
into this or all in detail later you can
稍后对此进行详细介绍
specify that that you want need specific
指定您想要的具体需求
JRE for your eclipse set some variables
为您的Eclipse设置一些变量
and then create a module API target
然后创建一个模块API目标
platform that's looking like this
看起来像这样的平台
so you see here all the our different
所以你在这里看到我们所有的不同
eclipse will use this and we will later
eclipse将使用它，我们稍后
answer why is this module and here we
回答为什么是这个模块，在这里我们
are of the sub-project so you can
属于子项目，因此您可以
organize your projects in main project
在主项目中组织您的项目
sub projects and this could look like
子项目，这看起来像
this and it adds some more information
这并添加了更多信息
like cloning a git repository again
就像再次克隆git存储库
doing something module target define
做一些模块目标定义
working sets in your workspace looking
工作区中的工作集
like this also in the introduce into
这样也可以在介绍中
detail later and then we define strings
稍后再详细说明，然后我们定义字符串
and let's talk about all these things
让我们来谈谈所有这些事情
now additionally you have more things
现在你还有更多的东西
that you can do in the setup which is
您可以在设置中执行的操作是
not in that set up like important
没有那样重要的设置
projects execute some launch
项目执行一些启动
configurations after the import of the
导入后的配置
projects or before whatever configure
项目或任何配置之前
Milan tasks to connect to bugzilla to
米兰任务连接到Bugzilla
github issues so that you have all the
github问题，以便您拥有所有
issues in in your workspace configure
工作区中的问题配置
baselines configure build tasks so that
基准配置构建任务，以便
you can connect to Jenkins and you can
你可以连接到詹金斯，你可以
also redirect URLs
也重定向URL
so let's see what what would your
让我们看看你会做什么
typical setup works so you typically
典型的设置工作正常，因此您通常
select the advanced node in the Clipper
在Clipper中选择高级节点
install choose one base IDE
安装选择一个基本的IDE
I normally use the ID for Eclipse
我通常将ID用于Eclipse
committers um then you select the
提交者，然后选择
project for example you want to work on
例如您要从事的项目
egit just select egit specify some
egit只是选择egit指定一些
variables usually that you just double
变量通常只是您的两倍
check that they're all correct for you
检查它们是否都适合您
specify a specific target platform for
指定特定的目标平台
that verify that everything's like you
验证一切都像你
want then press finish take a coffee and
要然后按完成喝咖啡，
after some minutes you have a workspace
几分钟后，您有了一个工作区
if you a I need with workspace and
如果您需要我的工作区，
everything is green or at least yellow
一切都是绿色或至少是黄色
warning bubbles that's normal but that's
警告气泡是正常的，但这是
simple um so let's go a little bit
简单嗯，让我们走一点
advance my platform workspace Eclipse
推进我的平台工作区Eclipse
platform workspace looks like this I see
平台工作区看起来像这样
all the things here on the left side and
这里所有的东西都在左侧
it's not files which is just working
不是文件才可以正常工作
search and then working sets their
搜索，然后将其设置为工作
projects and in projects they all the
项目和项目中的所有
files so it's really really large
文件，所以它真的非常大
workspace that I've set up and yeah work
我已经建立并工作的工作区
pretty well with it has some issues what
很好，它有一些问题
I did for not to set up this workspace
我没有设置这个工作区
is not select one project okay
不是选择一个项目好吗
resolution is very very bad but you can
分辨率非常非常差，但是您可以
imagine it yeah I'm selecting JTP de PD
想象是的，我正在选择JTP de PD
PD told SWT Equinox EMF and all these
PD告诉SWT Equinox EMF以及所有这些
prototypes collected is than the varied
收集的原型比变化多端的
appearance would that bum duck is closed
外观那屁股鸭是封闭的
down down down there plenty of
下来有很多
repositories to clone you have to select
要克隆的存储库，您必须选择
the target platform by default it says
默认说目标平台
here you get four point six that's not
在这里你得到四个点六不是
good choice for me to pull that set up
对我来说是个不错的选择
um so H is either oxygen or photons and
嗯，所以H是氧或光子，
then it takes really really really long
那真的需要很长时间
time
时间
and then okay that's annoying so it's
然后好吧，这很烦人
not that easy to write setups that work
编写工作并不容易
in that way so that you haven't if
这样，你就不会
you're in many projects that you could
你在很多项目中
explore once and and anything short
一劳永逸
together and but many of these setups
在一起，但其中许多设置
that that we find there are quite good
我们发现那里相当不错
so um we should learn from them and now
所以我们应该向他们学习
let's look I'll take a look at some of
让我们来看看一些
the projects and I will show you on what
这些项目，我将向您展示
they are doing arm and my reference
他们在做手臂，我的参考
projects are in fit self
项目适合自己
um that's always a good choice to have
嗯，这永远是一个不错的选择
even city-owned that this these are
即使是城市拥有的，这些都是
setups created by the office of course
当然由办公室创建的设置
platform there are plenty of examples
平台上有很多例子
which are really good
真的很好
the egit project does also a good job on
egit项目在以下方面也做得很好
writing an advanced setup and x text
编写高级设置和x文本
that's my thing so now let's go a little
那是我的事，所以现在让我们走一点
bit in 3d first of all you organized our
首先在3D中进行组织
set up in the main project and
在主项目中设置
sub-project but if you have a more
子项目，但如果您还有更多
advanced project so think about what can
高级项目，请考虑可以做什么
be done for all projects and what is
为所有项目完成的工作是什么
specific to a sub-project
特定于子项目
so as many as possible will go here in
所以尽可能多的人会去这里
this area which is the main project so
这是主要项目
specifying the target platform
指定目标平台
variables and preferences and so on and
变量和偏好等等
only that which is specific to a sub
仅特定于子
project you will specify and sub-project
您将指定的项目和子项目
like cloning specific repository if you
例如克隆特定的存储库
have repository sub-project like we have
有像我们一样的仓库子项目
got some extent we have I think nine
在某种程度上，我们认为九
depositories and you can select each of
存放处，您可以选择每个
them in the in the insulin
他们在胰岛素中
so if you just want to work on xx score
因此，如果您只想研究xx分数
it's like xx score and then if they and
就像xx分数，然后如果他们和
they set up is also very fast but you
他们的设置也非常快，但是您
can also choose anything from from xx
也可以从xx中选择任何内容
and it will clone anything so what is
它会克隆任何东西，所以
common that's the main question that you
常见的，这是你的主要问题
should answer and put as much as
应该回答并尽可能多地
possible up there in extracts we have
可能在提取物中
one set up and you like in JTTF so all
一个设置，并且您喜欢JTTF，因此所有
these parkade will sub projects but
这些停车场将子项目，但
there's also different possibility like
还有其他可能性，例如
the platform team does that's on the
平台团队做到了
installer I like and you see that you
我喜欢的安装程序，您会看到您
have several sub projects from which you
有几个子项目，您可以从中
can select to install and normally you
可以选择安装，通常情况下
would guess ok this is just a single
会想，这只是一个
setup
设定
no it's not it you can also modular eyes
不，不是，你也可以模块化的眼睛
your setups and say I'm having a logical
您的设置，并说我有逻辑
project containers you can specify this
您可以指定项目容器
here so here we are set up only for SWT
在这里，所以这里我们只为SWT设置
and and it participates through the
并且它通过
platform container and so it looks like
平台容器，所以看起来
as if it would be one in setup but it's
好像是安装程序中的一个，但是
actually get exploded next thing is
实际上爆炸的下一件事是
streams unusually streams are related
流异常地流相关
and would say to you to do the branches
会告诉你做分公司
that you could work on on the origin
你可以在原点上工作
repository and most set up so that I see
存储库和大多数设置，以便我看到
have just a single stream on they have
他们只有一条流
always the master screen I tend to you
总是主屏幕我倾向于你
have also maintenance screens so if you
还有维护屏幕，如果您
have and want to work on an already
有并且想要在已经
released project and you usually will
发布项目，您通常会
create a maintenance stream and yeah
创建维护流，是的
when you want to work on that you just
当您想为此工作时
can select that stream and it will check
可以选择该流，它将检查
out that branch for you
为你出去
old streams here and what we also see
这里的旧溪流，我们也看到了
here is um that a typical use case that
这是一个典型的用例
you can do in screen to rewrite
你可以在屏幕上重写
variables so usually you will have
变量，所以通常您将拥有
variables defined somewhere above and
变量定义在上方和
you override this form specifically to
您可以专门覆盖此表格
streams or specific to sub projects one
流或特定于子项目之一
thing that you may not have seen a
你可能没有看过的东西
redirects this is also something which
重定向这也是
you will see many times in the on set
你会在现场看到很多次
ups
UPS
actually this is here the JTP set up to
实际上，这是JTP设置的
lead instead of himself this requires a
领导而不是自己，这需要一个
so I'm firing this of that setup and the
所以我将这个设置和
redirects I have to have set up ethical
重定向我必须建立道德
and the earth after we checked it off
我们检查完之后的大地
because she wants you edit the set up
因为她要你编辑设置
which is on the clip took off but we
剪辑上的那个起飞了，但是我们
wanted to edit it on during the same set
想在同一组中对其进行编辑
up in our workspace and this is done
在我们的工作区中，就完成了
with this trick actually this is an old
有了这个技巧，实际上这是一个古老的
style on there so a redirection task
那里的样式，所以重定向任务
that can do this okay because that's
可以做到这一点，因为那是
good to know at the Eclipse Phineas its
很高兴在Eclipse Phineas上了解它
grade has a very first step in the
年级是第一步
installation process here but there's
安装过程在这里，但有
also another use case for this
还有另一个用例
redirection tasks usually if you start
重定向任务，通常如果您开始
downloading or installing something then
然后下载或安装某些东西
you will see are all all these public
您将看到所有这些公共场所
repositories that are career it here so
在这里是事业的仓库
accessing the internet but what is if
访问互联网，但是如果
you are sitting behind the firewall and
你坐在防火墙后面，
you can't access these things then you
你无法访问这些东西，那么你
have to make it happen that
必须做到这一点
all that you address here or what in
您在此处或其中输入的所有内容
tries to query is the redirected to some
尝试查询被重定向到一些
internal location you could set up Nexus
您可以设置Nexus的内部位置
server and just provide a mirror of that
服务器，并提供一个镜像
repository our customers that have this
存放具有此功能的客户
problem or they can't go outside from
问题或他们不能从外面走
there from there from their computer so
从他们的电脑那里那里
they need to execute a setup without
他们需要执行设置而无需
accessing the internet and this is where
访问互联网，这是在哪里
you can use redirects next thing that
您可以使用重定向功能
you you typically will do is install
您通常会做的就是安装
additional features to your to your
您的附加功能
eclipse we see here are that yeah we
月食，我们看到这里是，是的，我们
accessing several repositories to
访问多个存储库以
install additional features on on
在上安装其他功能
eclipse we see here are the famous any
我们看到这里的日食是著名的
edit tools and the target platform
编辑工具和目标平台
editing feature from the Kaibab able and
Kaibab的编辑功能
special thing is here they are not
特殊的是这里不是
optional so it's not mandatory to
可选，因此不是强制性的
transfer all these these tools for the
将所有这些工具转移给
like for the case that one of these
对于其中一种情况
repositories is broken and the setup
存储库被破坏，安装程序
will still perform when you knock that
敲门时仍会执行
and them as option but there's a matter
和他们作为选择，但有一个问题
of taste if you really want to have some
如果您真的想要一些口味
tools in your setup in in the setup that
设置中的工具
all the users of your setup will have
您设置的所有用户都将拥有
their other means to do this in this
他们这样做的其他方式
case there are that project decides to
如果有项目决定
add to install that feature that's the
添加以安装该功能
example from our X text here we have
这里的X文字示例
splitted on the installation of the p2
在P2的安装分裂
director tasks not to the main project
导演的任务不交给主项目
but we have additional tools that are
但是我们还有其他工具
installed in a sub-project
安装在子项目中
and especially this thing here some
特别是这个东西在这里
users of of extract don't want you to
提取物的用户不希望您
have Milan installed and all the box
安装了米兰和所有箱子
from Bugzilla or all the old stuff are
来自Bugzilla或所有旧资料
there so we decided to make a separate
在那里，我们决定单独制作一个
sub project where we install Milan
我们安装米兰的子项目
features with and then also do the
功能，然后也可以
remaining category tasks there so you
剩下的类别任务在那里
can decide do I want to see my issues in
可以决定要查看我的问题
in the workspace or I don't I want this
在工作区中还是我不想要这个
then also the Eclipse installation
然后还有Eclipse安装
becomes neener another thing that you
变得更加内在
will see is the resource creation task
将看到的是资源创建任务
this is happening a very beginning of
这是一个非常开始的时刻
your installation process so you can
您的安装过程，以便您可以
create files at a certain position and
在特定位置创建文件并
for example you often see the dialog
例如，您经常看到对话框
settings file for its 4jt UI so they you
4jt用户界面的设置文件，以便您
configure your your workspace like it
像这样配置您的工作区
should be layout and then it's export
应该是布局，然后导出
that that settings and use it in your
该设置并在您的
setup so everyone will see the same
设置，这样每个人都会看到相同的
feeling there what I also saw is that
在那里我也看到的是
for amazing people on the new use may be
对于新用途的惊人人来说可能是
may and recognize this nasty error
可能并认识到这个讨厌的错误
markers on the palms that some plug-in
手掌上的一些插件标记
is not recognized to participate in a
不被认可参加
lifecycle
生命周期
it's it's not really from here back it's
这不是真的从这里回来
just it's a bug that it's bothering me
只是一个困扰我的错误
and you can configure this in a file
您可以在文件中进行配置
that you just ignore that and that setup
你只是忽略了那个设置
here yeah copies just the content of
是的，这里只是复制内容
that fire to a certain position and then
射击到某个位置然后
you won't get this errors another
你不会再得到这个错误
interesting thing that I saw from a
我从一个有趣的东西
cliff smart home is that's ex x-rated
悬崖智能家居是X级的
thing if you want want to generate your
如果你想生成你的东西
ex ex grammar you will you will need an
前语法，您将需要一个
it is no jar on
它没有罐子
on your file system which is not
在您的文件系统上
available at eclipse from our service
从我们的服务中可以在Eclipse中获得
and it must be at a certain position and
它必须在某个位置，
you can actually use resource copy and
您实际上可以使用资源复制和
specify an HTTP URL to download file to
指定一个HTTP URL将文件下载到
some location to a workspace variables
工作区变量的某些位置
are very important of course you don't
当然不是很重要
need really variables if you specify
如果指定，则需要真正的变量
everything hard-coded but I like
一切都是硬编码的，但我喜欢
variables to see then then I see okay
变量，然后看，我知道了
this is on the actual versions that I'm
这是在我的实际版本上
using these are the these are the URLs
使用这些是这些URL
that I'm using and I can change it there
我正在使用，我可以在那里更改它
it's very prominent there and they are
那里很显眼，他们
just used to this case there's to see a
只是习惯了这种情况
configuration for the Milan tasks and
米兰任务的配置和
they are just using this variable and so
他们只是在使用这个变量，所以
you and variables you can also overwrite
您和变量也可以覆盖
so you can say okay I have my novel set
所以你可以说我有我的小说集
up but for the certain stream it's
向上，但对于某些流
different and you just change that
不同，你只是改变那个
variable and in that configuration next
变量，然后在该配置中
axis looks like this we have plenty of
轴看起来像这样，我们有很多
repositories that we are clearing and so
我们正在清理的存储库等
we define all these these repositories
我们定义所有这些存储库
as variables we also specify on versions
作为变量，我们也在版本上指定
here and this is how you could use
在这里，这就是你可以使用的方式
variables target platform is very
目标平台的变量非常大
important if you or develop on Eclipse
如果您或在Eclipse上进行开发，则很重要
plugins and there are two ways to to
插件，有两种方法可以
write target platforms one thing is
写目标平台的一件事是
module target platforms and as you know
模块目标平台，如您所知
that you can of course define target
您当然可以定义目标
platform definitions and oome also
平台定义和oome
allows to use target platform definition
允许使用目标平台定义
files in the egit project dustless which
egit项目中的文件无尘
is also causing the trouble if you want
如果你想也造成麻烦
to have an workspace with egit and
有一个带有egit和
others because the module target
其他，因为模块目标
platform it's your friend there modular
平台，您的朋友在那里模块化
because yeah you can be
因为是的，你可以
modules and all the projects that you're
模块和您正在执行的所有项目
collecting for your setup they build up
收集他们建立的设置
one single target platform later and the
一个单一的目标平台，然后
typical thing on how module tab looks
模块选项卡外观的典型内容
like is that you have a so-called
就像你有一个所谓的
chocolate there content repository lists
巧克力那里内容存储库列表
for all the Eclipse releases you can
对于所有Eclipse版本，您都可以
also extend this in a in the extract
也将其扩展到摘录中
setup we have changed this because we
设置我们已经更改了此设置，因为我们
also need tag platform for staging
还需要标签平台进行分阶段
repositories and you don't have that by
存储库，而您没有
default here in anything in that setup
该设置中的任何内容都默认为此处
piece this repository lists are
该存储库清单是
inherited from parent project and it
从父项目继承而来
usually just contains a and their
通常只包含和
release trains
发布火车
so until proton but if you want to have
所以直到质子，但如果你想拥有
set up with proton staging in closet
在壁橱中设置质子分级
Ares then we have to do something and
然后，我们必须做些什么，
then look at X text what we also see
然后看看X文字我们也看到了
here is what's with oxygen and photo no
这是氧气和照片的东西，否
it's not new year and that's quite nasty
这不是新的一年，那真是令人讨厌
thing recently there was someone who
最近有件事
tried to work on SWT and just execute it
尝试在SWT上工作并执行
on the DM setup facility and it was
在DM设置工具上，
broken because they were we're not
破碎，因为他们是我们不是
prepared for philtrum you could not
为哲学做准备，你不能
select yeah of course it could select a
选择是的，当然可以选择一个
photo nurse at our platform but then
在我们平台上的照片护士，然后
everything is broken because the setup
一切都坏了，因为设置
was not prepared for it and so every
没有为此做好准备，所以每个
setup actually has really per release to
安装程序实际上每个版本都有
add an additional repository list to
向其中添加其他存储库列表
make this work maybe this is something
做这项工作也许这是东西
you can think about at if there could be
你可以考虑一下是否有
something like latest or so that not all
像最新的东西，所以不是全部
the report are set ups have to be
报告设置必须
changed when a new release cut is coming
即将发布新版本时更改
out so yeah
出来啊
so you have to take care of that the
所以你必须照顾
then for my platform watch place you see
那么对于我的平台观看地点
the module target consists of very very
模块目标由非常非常
many tablets or contributing to this
许多平板电脑或对此有所贡献
platform and that's not easy either then
平台，那也不容易
because often you have the effect that
因为通常你会产生
when you execute that that you will fail
当您执行那将失败
and good you have to read to read what
好，你必须阅读以阅读
is the missing requirement and sometimes
是缺少的要求，有时
it's indicating that that the setups are
这表明设置是
not correct or yeah yeah yes check that
不正确或是，是的，请检查
we cumbersome to make this really work
我们很难做到这一点
with many many projects at once in this
一次有很多项目
case it's okay yes j-th requires a
如果可以的话，第j个要求
project which is called jaga JD I
名为jaga JD I的项目
testify project and I didn't I try to
证明项目，但我没有尝试
observe actually do not find that in the
观察实际上并没有发现
whole repository oh so seems to be a
整个仓库，哦，看来是一个
bargain and JT setup yeah and they don't
讨价还价和JT设置是的，他们没有
carry much anymore yeah hopefully this
携带更多，希望这
helps here um and also sharing the
帮助这里，并分享
slides helps I wanted to make this
幻灯片可以帮助我实现这一目标
better
更好
[Music]
[音乐]
maybe we should you should me show me
也许我们应该让我告诉我
this trick what what what do you see
这个把戏是什么，你看到了什么
also hear onto in the mono targets is
也听到单声道目标是
this thing here it looks strange on the
这东西在这里看起来很奇怪
that's the definition so you see your I
那就是定义，所以你看到你的我
have a requirement which says I won't
有一个要求说我不会
require anything and I'm using a source
需要任何东西，我正在使用来源
located to to
位于
you do this what this does is the sauce
你做这是酱
locator is scanning the file systems or
定位器正在扫描文件系统或
the repository in this case locating
在这种情况下，存储库位于
nested project so it search for projects
嵌套项目，以便它搜索项目
and whenever it finds something where it
每当发现它在哪里
can derive I you connect coordinates
可以得出我连接坐标
from then it will add this to the
从那时起，它将添加到
reporter to the target platform so on
记者到目标平台等等
this way you can add projects that are
这样，您可以添加
in your workspace to the target platform
在您的工作区中到目标平台
and this style crater is something that
这个火山口就是
you built at I talked with Ike I said I
你建在我和艾克交谈时我说我
did not like that in sitio the
在西提奥不喜欢那样
requirements are listed one by one then
需求一一列出
you have to maintain the Stata Ike I
你必须维护Stata Ike I
said that it would locate in seedy old
说，它将位于旧的
also projects that I don't want to be
我也不想成为的项目
part of the target platform so and
目标平台的一部分，因此
therefore he lists this one by one but
因此他一一列出
the easiest way of course is if it's
最简单的方法当然是
fine
精细
you just use the star operator you
你只用星号运算符
should take care of preferences what
应该照顾喜好什么
preferences want do you want to that are
首选项想要您想要的是
set forth for the workspace and there
为工作空间而定
are some tools that can help you to on
有一些工具可以帮助您
to create the preference tasks in your
在您的中创建首选项任务
setup
设定
otherwise it's would be really it's it's
否则将会是真的
hard to write one preference by the
很难通过
other here's the red quarter so when you
其他这里是红色区，所以当你
press on this bundle above a year and
一年以上按此捆绑包，然后
then change some preference in your
然后改变你的一些偏好
workspace preferences
工作区首选项
and only recognizes and put this into
并只认出并放入
your own setup it's a nice thing the
您自己的设置是一件好事
other button year this is also
其他按钮的年份也是
interesting this import preferences so
有趣的此导入首选项，因此
you have good workspace you know that
你有很好的工作空间，你知道
you can export a preference file and
您可以导出首选项文件，然后
then you can use this dialog to select
然后您可以使用此对话框选择
from some of them you can do this by
从其中一些中，您可以通过
futures and say ok I want to show
期货说好，我想展示
whitespace characters that's the
空格字符是
preference that that I want to in my a
我想要的偏好
my setup and then take this over that's
我的设置，然后接管那是
quite nice
相当不错
so which preferences should you usually
所以你通常应该选择哪些偏好
consider to for a full workspace setup
考虑到完整的工作空间设置
let's have a look at a little bit at
让我们来看看
what we doing expects some of them um
我们期待他们中的一些人
one of the most important things in
最重要的事情之一
coding do do a workspace encoding agree
编码做一个工作区编码同意吗
on one and utf-8 is usually good choice
在一个和utf-8通常是不错的选择
on Windows machines you have default
在Windows计算机上，您具有默认值
windows 1252 you import a project
Windows 1252您导入一个项目
without any preference and then start
没有任何偏好，然后开始
creating new resource and they are
创建新资源，他们是
wrongly encoded or it'll actually
编码错误，否则实际上
actually um for workspace in for filing
实际上是在工作空间中用于归档
coding and the other thing is new lines
编码，另一件事是换行
what is the new line format file for
什么是新的行格式文件
your created files is it unique style or
您创建的文件是唯一样式还是
window start this should be also
窗口开始，这也应该
something that that you configure and
您配置的东西
actually I'm a friend of making this
其实我是做这个的朋友
project specific so that you check this
特定于项目的项目，以便您检查
in for each and every project and don't
在每个项目中都不要
rely on the fact that that you setup
依赖于您设置的事实
your project with whom if you don't do
您的项目，如果您不与谁合作
that yeah you don't have the preferences
是的，你没有偏好
and may create wrong encoded files also
并可能还会创建错误的编码文件
important is JDT settings which compiler
重要的是JDT设置哪个编译器
version
版
want to see a set also and that's also
我也想看一套
one important thing you should to
您应该做的一件事
consider to configure content types
考虑配置内容类型
that's strange why actually want to show
这很奇怪，为什么实际上想要展示
you why this is a screenshot from from
你为什么这是来自的截图
the yogic profiler doing a text search
瑜伽分析器进行文本搜索
on a large workspace and these red
在一个很大的工作区上，这些红色
things are blocking things so actually
事情阻碍了事情，所以实际上
there is code that is executed in during
有在执行期间的代码
text search which are blocking the
文字搜索阻止了
threats during the search and I look
搜索过程中的威胁，我看起来
into this and actually it's here
进入这个，实际上它在这里
somewhere you can't read this it tries
某个你看不懂的地方
to figure out if a certain file that is
找出某个文件是否
now scans has binary content if you have
现在扫描包含二进制内容（如果有）
a content type defined for that file
为该文件定义的内容类型
extension and can decide this upfront so
扩展，可以预先决定，因此
it says okay this is a text file I can
它说好吧，这是一个文本文件，我可以
evaluate that otherwise it goes into the
评估，否则它会进入
file starts reading the file and tries
文件开始读取文件并尝试
to decode on the characters that he
对他的角色进行解码
finds and then and this course is
找到，然后这门课是
something really internal in Java IO
Java IO中真正内部的东西
where there's a blocking cache so if you
有阻塞缓存的地方，如果
have large amounts of files we'll
我们将拥有大量文件
probably which you don't have a content
可能您没有内容
type then this can be done rating of
输入即可完成对
search performance actually this came up
搜索效果实际上是这样
when I worked on X text and then I found
当我处理X文本时，我发现
that and this is one of the new features
那是新功能之一
in xx 213 now that we generate content
在xx 213中，现在我们生成了内容
types for our DSL files and of course
DSL文件的类型，当然
for all the existing file formats that
对于所有现有的文件格式
we have so especially for extent files
对于扩展文件，我们尤其如此
this was a game changer because I have
这是一个改变游戏规则的人，因为我有
large amounts of extend files in my work
我的工作中有大量扩展文件
space and they're slow slowly search
空间，他们慢慢搜索
um so also interesting here for me
嗯，对我来说也很有趣
enough you can import formatting
足以导入格式
settings that's also good each project
每个项目都很好的设置
has different ideas how to format code
有不同的想法如何格式化代码
and if you have a certain format profile
并且如果您具有特定的格式配置文件
and you can just use the preference
您可以使用首选项
settings here and import that settings
设置并导入该设置
can also specify that you don't want to
也可以指定您不想
have this as global preferences but user
将此作为全局首选项，但用户
preferences store it differently in a
偏好设置将其不同地存储在
user setup um correct me if I'm wrong
用户设置um如果我错了请纠正我
so by this annotation it goes to the
因此，通过此注释，它转到
user space right okay thanks next
用户空间正确，谢谢，接下来
working sets dynamic working search list
工作集动态工作搜索列表
that's nice feature you usually if you
那通常是个不错的功能
have your many projects then you want to
有很多项目，那么你想
organize them in into your core projects
将它们组织到您的核心项目中
test projects UI projects whatever and
测试项目UI项目
that's this you can nicely define with
这就是您可以很好地定义的
dynamic working sets you have different
您拥有不同的动态工作集
options here so you see okay I'm
选项在这里，所以你知道我是
platform your eyes all the repository
让您的眼睛站满所有存储库
all projects that are in the same
同一项目中的所有项目
repository as one of the projects in
仓库作为以下项目之一
that I know and excluding other
我知道并且排除其他
of projects that are contained in other
包含在其他项目中的项目
working sets so this you can define and
工作集，以便您可以定义和
you see this is another set up it looks
您会看到这是另一个设置
nearly the same so you can just look at
几乎一样，所以你可以看看
this and that's all the options that you
这就是你所有的选择
can do it you can create and expression
可以做到，你可以创造和表达
that can say this and this and this or
可以说这个，这个和这个，或者
expression not expression say must be in
表达而不是表达必须在
a certain repository must be a certain
某个存储库必须是某个
location must have a certain nature must
位置必须具有一定的性质
have configure the Builder whatever very
已经非常配置Builder
rarely you have to specify an order that
很少需要指定一个命令
something has to happen before usually
通常必须先发生一些事情
oomph does a good job on on that and the
oomph在这方面做得很好，并且
orders are normally good and but
订单通常很好，但是
sometimes it's necessary that you say
有时候你有必要说
this has to happen before the other
这必须在另一个之前发生
thing and then you can also say if you
事情，然后你也可以说，如果你
specify predecessors of my task you know
指定我知道的任务的前身
is working well with agate what about
与玛瑙合作良好
subversion if you I have customers and
如果您有客户，请颠覆
we still avoid well using subversion
我们仍然避免很好地使用Subversion
there's no subversion import asked as a
没有要求将subversion导入作为
trick doing this um you can specify team
可以这样做，你可以指定团队
project sets and export the team project
项目集并导出团队项目
set I'll copy this to a resource
设置我将其复制到资源
creation task put this into a certain
创建任务将其确定
location then and then you can say again
位置，然后您可以再说一遍
importing that a team project set and
导入该团队项目集并
then automatically ooomph will also
然后自动放大
import that from from authority you can
从权威机构进口，你可以
specify the issue tracker so Milan tasks
指定问题跟踪程序，以便米兰执行任务
queries um either for crack for Bugzilla
查询um以获得Bugzilla的破解
or also for github and when you do this
或者也适用于github，当您执行此操作时
and all the tasks will be in your
所有的任务都将在您的
workspace looks like this
工作区看起来像这样
we have organized last year nice thing
去年我们组织了一件好事
here is um it is really good searchable
这是很好的可搜索性
if you have this all in your in the
如果您拥有所有这些
workspace and can just search is there a
工作区，可以只搜索那里
balk which contains that stack what we
阻止包含该堆栈的内容
are also doing in looks really right
看起来也不错
running out of time have to hurry up we
时间不多了要赶快我们
have continuing build tasks so that you
具有持续的构建任务，以便您
can compute the build chops
可以计算出印章
same is done here for EMF CEO so connect
对EMF CEO也是一样，因此请连接
to Jenkins you can even trigger then the
对于詹金斯，您甚至可以触发
votes from there you can see build
从那里可以看到投票
screen you can retrigger the build
屏幕上您可以重新触发构建
that's nice
真好
and okay that's small thing um you will
好的，那是一件小事，你会的
recognize that some setups are having a
认识到某些设置具有
nice icon and that's a trick to do this
漂亮的图标，这是做到这一点的技巧
you have a branding and for annotation
您有品牌和注释
and then you can specify an image UI for
然后您可以为
that you can specify that not only a
您可以指定不仅
project set of your user and other
用户和其他人的项目集
setups what does this used for let's
设置这是用来做什么的
take a look at my user setup I'm always
看看我的用户设置，我总是
installing your kit so that's nothing
安装您的工具包，什么都没有
that I want to add to a project setup
我想添加到项目设置中
and force other people to install your
并强迫其他人安装您的
kit but I always have the your kitten's
包，但我总是有你小猫的
extension there and this I can specify
扩展那里，我可以指定
in the user setup as taken care the
在用户设置中请注意
workspace setup arm I'm using to add
我要添加的工作区设置臂
additional things to my target platform
目标平台上的其他内容
like in the XX SDK to might cut from
例如XX SDK中的
target project so this you can therefore
目标项目，因此您可以
you can use the workspace setup or the
您可以使用工作区设置或
installation setup you like okay I think
你喜欢的安装设置好吧，我认为
I ran out of time actually uh yeah so
我实际上没时间了，嗯，所以
I'm almost through but I think I would
我快要走了，但我想我会
say okay I will stop right now and yeah
说好吧，我现在就停下来，是的
ask your questions over that so okay
这么问你的问题
I don't think there's a chance to do
我认为没有机会
this it's not not a preference and we do
这不是优先选择，我们做到了
this nasty tricks also that was the last
这个讨厌的把戏也是最后
thing that I did did want to show is in
我确实想展示的东西在
xx we have the problem that that we are
xx我们有一个问题，就是
using a Gradle okay this maybe not be a
使用Gradle好吧，这可能不是一个
problem but we have to plumb that they
问题，但我们必须探究他们
have a multi project multi repository
有一个多项目的多仓库
set up and you will usually want to have
设置好之后，您通常会希望拥有
want to debug code from another project
要调试另一个项目中的代码
from another repository and this is not
从另一个存储库，这不是
how build ship works it only allows this
建造船的工作方式仅允许
within one aggregate which is one
在一个聚合中
repository and we're literally creating
存储库，我们实际上是在创建
a project above that but which
一个以上的项目，但是
aggregates all the aggregates and
汇总所有汇总，并且
therefore we have to create a file and
因此我们必须创建一个文件并
modify that depending on which pro
修改哪个取决于哪个亲
repositories you actually selected so it
您实际选择的存储库
can really do nasty stuff of okay thanks
真的可以做讨厌的事情，谢谢
for joining
加入
don't forget to vote if you vote minus
如果您的投票减号，别忘了投票
one then please explain why it can be
然后请解释一下为什么可以
better but thank you for listening and
更好，但感谢您的收听和
gear available for further questions
齿轮可用于进一步的问题
thank you
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]